http://solidcolorneckties.com/pages/privacy

Privacy Policy | TieMart
– TieMart, Inc.
Skip to content
Submit
Close search
Just added to your cart
Qty:
View cart ()
Continue shopping
Save an extra 15% off clearance with SALE15 + free shipping at $20!
FAQ
CONTACT US »
SHIPPING »
ORDER HELP »
DISCOUNTS »
RETURNS »
SWATCHES »
REVIEWS »
ABOUT OUR TIES »
ABOUT US »
Privacy Policy
TieMart, Inc. operates www.tiemart.com (the Site) as well as selling on various marketplaces. This privacy policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you use any of these websites or marketplaces.
Personal information we collect
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”.
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. Please refer to the "Do we use cookies?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
- "Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
- “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information”.
We also collect information from you when you register on the site, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, request free color swatches, submit a custom tie request or participate in another site feature.
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
How do we use your information?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
- Communicate with you, including to better service you in responding to your customer service requests;
- Quickly process your transactions;
- Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud;
- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature;
- To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
- When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services. If you would no longer like to receive promotional email from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?"
- If you abandon your shopping cart without completing the order, you will receive a follow-up email from us within 36 hours with a link to your saved shopping cart.
- If you place an order, you will receive a follow-up message from us about 10 days after your order.
- Information collected about gift recipients is only used to fulfill the gift purchase and not used for marketing purposes.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
How do we protect visitor information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.
Do we use "cookies"?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Third party vendors show our ads on sites on the internet. Third party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. Users may opt out of this by going to the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (i.e. Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, etc.) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.
For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.
The above sites will provide more information for you on how to remove cookies from your device. However, this may impact your ability to use some features of our website such as the shopping cart.
Behavioral advertising
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by using the links below:
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
- Google: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
- Bing: https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
Third party links
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include TieMart, Inc. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store. (You can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy.) We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site. (You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.)
We also use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet. TieMart, Inc. and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to your website.
Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
We may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.
Your rights
You have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below. There may be a small charge for this service.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
Every email subscription sent contains a link to unsubscribe at the bottom of the email. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.
Data retention
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
Do not track
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
Changes to our policy
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
Online policy only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Questions and feedback
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by email at service@tiemart.com or by mail using the details provided below:
TieMart, Inc. Re: Privacy Compliance Officer525 Morris Ave.Mundelein, IL 60060USA
We send awesome emails. Wanna see?
© 2020 TieMart, Inc.525 Morris Ave. Mundelein, IL 60060 USACall Us: 847-566-5980Fax Us: 847-388-4704
Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection
